{
    "question": "Membuat kalimat simple present dengan kata yg d bawah:    1.know\r\n2.write\r\n3.cut\r\n4.drive\r\n5.drink\r\n6.give\r\n7.become\r\n8.overcome\r\n9.keep\r\n10.set\r\n11.hang\r\n12.sing\r\n13.tell\r\n14.shoot\r\n15.grow\r\n16.meet\r\n17.undo\r\n18.feel\r\n19.cost\r\n20.come",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": ".know<br>2.write<br>3.cut<br>4.drive<br>5.drink<br>6.give<br>7.become<br>8.overcome<br>9.keep<br>10.set<br>11.hang<br>12.sing<br>13.tell<br>14.shoot<br>15.grow<br>16.meet<br>17.undo<br>18.feel<br>19.cost<br><span>20.come:0</span>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "1. I know if he always glance at me<br>2. I write a story every sunday<br>3. He cuts his hair every one month<br>4.She drive car with her friends every sunday morning<br>5. The children drinks a glass of milk every day<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "definisi-positive-adjective-itu-apa-dan-contohnya-569",
            "question": "Definisi positive adjective itu apa ?? dan contohnya ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Definisi nya sudah diterangkan oleh mbak Karina, Yaitu berfungsi untuk menambahkan keterangan kata benda (noun),\u00a0 saya menambahkan contohnya saja <br><br>He has beautiful garden = adjective -&gt; beautiful noun nya garden<br><br>He has sharp eyes = adjective -&gt; sharp dari noun eyes<br><br>He loves to paint beautiful home -&gt; adjective beautiful dari noun home <br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-beda-auxilary-amp-operator-siapa-penemu-font-old-english-907",
            "question": "-Apa beda Auxilary &amp; Operator?    -Siapa penemu font Old English?\r\n -Kapan Bahasa Inggris masuk ke Indonesia?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "gaktau ee kak bntar takcarikan yha<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "narrative-text-yang-bagus-dan-jarang-di-dengar-orang-797",
            "question": "Narrative text yang bagus dan jarang di dengar orang??",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The story snow white<br>In earlier times there lived a , who named Snow White . He lived with his aunt and uncle because his parents died . One day she heard her uncle and aunt talking about leaving Snow White in the castle because they wanted to go to America and they did not have enough money to take Snow White with them . princess Snow White did not want her uncle and aunt to do this . So he decided to escape .<br><br><span>\u00a0The next day he ran away from home when her aunt and uncle were having breakfast , he fled into the wood . In the wood she felt very tired and hungry . Then she saw this cottage . She knocked but no one answered her so she went inside and felt asleep Meanwhile seven dwarfs came home from his work . They get into . There, they found Snow White woke up from his sleep . He saw the dwarfs . The dwarf said : \" What is your name ? &#039; Snow White said , \" My name is Snow White . \" One dwarf said , \" If you want , you can stay here with us . &#039; Snow White tells all about her story . Then daughter snow and the seven dwarves are now living happily ever after .</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bedanya-conditional-type-1-2-dan-3-320",
            "question": "Apa bedanya conditional type 1, 2 dan 3 ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "if conditional sentences? beda tenses-nya, sama fact-nya",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Type 1 = Real / Present Conditional (terjadi sekarang)<br>Form = If + S + V1..., I + will + V1...<br>Example = If I have money, I will treat you<br>Meaning = it may/ may not happen. Jadi artinya bisa terjadi atau tidak.<br><br>Type 2 = Contrary to the present fact (bertentangan sama yang terjadi pada kenyataan)<br>Form = If + S + V2..., I + would + V1...<br>Example = <br>a. If I <u>had money,</u> I would treat you<br>b. If I <u>were</u> you, I would leave him<br>Meaning = <br>a1. I don&#039;t <u>have money</u>, so I dont treat you, or<br>a2. I don&#039;t treat you, because I don&#039;t have money<br>b. I<u>&#039;m</u> not you, so I don&#039;t leave him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 2, penyataan dalam v2, arti dalam v1)<br><br>Type 3 <br>Form = If + S + had + V3..., I + would + have + V3...<br>Example = <br>a. If I had had money, I would have treated you<br>b. If my father had got marred again, my mother would have killed him<br>Meaning = <br>a. I didn&#039;t have money, so I didn&#039;t treat you<br>b. My father didn&#039;t get married again, so my mother didn&#039;t kill him<br>(intinya kalau conditional 3, penyataan dalam v3, arti dalam v2)<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-soal-soal-persuading-195",
            "question": "Contoh soal soal persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Why don\u2019t you\ntry our special drink bandrek to warm up your body?\n\n\n\n\n<br><span>\nIf I were you, I\nwould \u2026 ?</span>\n<span>\n\u00a0I\u2019m sure you are\non the right track.?</span>\n\n\n<br><span>\n\u00a0<span>I bet you could\ndo it.?</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "did-he-has-a-bad-seat-203",
            "question": "Did he has a bad seat?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "dia memiliki kursi yang buruk?",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ini merupakan idiom dari suatu kondisi yang kurang nyaman pada perusahaan<br>contoh lain adalah\u00a0<br>His job is kind of hand wringing profession.<br>Pekerjaan dia adalah pekerjaan yang kadang meremas dirinya.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "in-pairscomplete-the-question-with-corret-simple-present-form-572",
            "question": "\u00a0in pairs,complete the question with corret simple present form. 1. A: ........ to the radio every morning? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: Yes, I listen to it every morning \u00a0 2. A: .......... in Manchester\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: No, \u00a0he lives in Newcastle\u00a0 3. A: ......... the guitar?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: Yes,she plays the guitar and the piano.\u00a0 4. A: \u00a0......... TV every morning?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: No,they watch is most evening.\u00a0 5. A: \u00a0......... To school every day?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: She usually goes to school at 06.00 a.m. .",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. do<br>2. does he<br>3. does she play<br>4. do they watch<br>5. what time does she usually go",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1.\u00a0do you<br>2. does he live<br>3. does she play<br>4. do they watch<br>5. what time does she usually go",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantu-nyusun-kata-kata-ne-jadi-klimat-yg-bner-ya-yang-dimulai-dri-452",
            "question": "Bantu nyusun kata-kata ne jadi klimat yg bner ya yang dimulai dri yg bergaris bawah sama bantu buatkan CONDITIONAL SENTENCE TIPE 2    arrange the jumbled words to form meaningful sentences,starting with the underlined words.\r\n1. phone-puppet-his-invite-the-I-number-my-see-Finto-know-will-if-show-to-I-at-place\r\n2. and-holiday-Bali-if-have-will-his-Lombok-long-go-year-Mr. Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\u00a0mohon di bantu",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. If\u00a0 I know his phone number, I will invite Finto to the puppet show at my place.<br>2. If Mr. Kukuh and his family go to Bali, they will have a long holiday to Lombok this year.<br>Sorry kalau salah, baru pemula hehehe<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mohon-berikan-contoh-soal-mengenai-persuading-459",
            "question": "Mohon berikan contoh soal mengenai persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Persuading adalah mempengaruhi lawan bicara untuk melakukan atau mengerjakan sesuatu seperti yang diharapkan pihak pertama<br><br>COntoh\u00a0<br>Mengajak bermain basket<br>Hi my brother, would you be so kind to accompany me playing basketball? I will give you a chocolate if you would like to play it with me.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "when do you go to school about 10 minutes later?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}